[
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Voyages Extraordinaires",
        "Percy Jackson & the Olympians",
        "Twilight"
      ],
      "question": "In which book series does 'Cedric Diggory' appear?",
      "tags": [
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "correctAnswer": "Advocaat",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Grappa",
        "Brandy",
        "Grand Marnier"
      ],
      "question": "What liqueur goes into making a 'snowball' cocktail?",
      "tags": [
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Film & TV",
      "correctAnswer": "Sigourney Weaver",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Natalie Portman",
        "Kate Winslet",
        "Helen Mirren"
      ],
      "question": "Which actress has featured in films including Avatar and Alien?",
      "tags": [
        "film_and_tv"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "correctAnswer": "George R. R. Martin",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Stephen King",
        "Jack Vance",
        "Edgar Rice Burroughs"
      ],
      "question": "Which author wrote 'A Game of Thrones'?",
      "tags": [
        "fantasy",
        "literature",
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "correctAnswer": "the ecology of any individual species",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "crayfish",
        "crayfish",
        "birds"
      ],
      "question": "What is Autecology the study of?",
      "tags": [
        "science"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "correctAnswer": "Belgium",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Italy",
        "Bosnia & Herzegovina",
        "Brazil"
      ],
      "question": "In which country would you find the city of Bruges?",
      "tags": [
        "geography"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "correctAnswer": "Nepal",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Sudan",
        "Myanmar",
        "Tanzania"
      ],
      "question": "Kathmandu is the capital city of which country?",
      "tags": [
        "capital_cities",
        "geography"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "correctAnswer": "Tennis",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Badminton",
        "Cycling",
        "Basketball"
      ],
      "question": "With which sport is Steffi Graf associated?",
      "tags": [
        "people",
        "sport"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "correctAnswer": "a branch of geology that studies sediments",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "bones",
        "the study and treatment of diseases of the urogenital tract",
        "the eyes"
      ],
      "question": "What is Sedimentology the study of?",
      "tags": [
        "science"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "correctAnswer": "Vietnam",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Cambodia",
        "Korea",
        "Laos"
      ],
      "question": "Which country was divided into North And South in 1954 after the French colonial government was forced out?",
      "tags": [
        "colonialism",
        "history",
        "countries",
        "geography",
        "1950's"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Film & TV",
      "correctAnswer": "A shadowy freedom fighter plots to overthrow the tyrannical government.",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Two men searching for work in 1920s Mexico convince an old prospector to help them mine for gold.",
        "A New York City mob boss transfers control of his empire to his reluctant son.",
        "An Army officer serving in Vietnam is tasked with assassinating a renegade Special Forces Colonel."
      ],
      "question": "What is the plot of the movie V for Vendetta?",
      "tags": [
        "film",
        "film_and_tv"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Film & TV",
      "correctAnswer": "Elton John",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Paul McCartney",
        "Paul Simon",
        "Michael Jackson"
      ],
      "question": "Who Wrote The Music To The 1994 Movie “The Lion King”",
      "tags": [
        "film",
        "disney",
        "soundtracks",
        "1990's",
        "film_and_tv"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "correctAnswer": "Cabbage ",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Onions",
        "Carrots",
        "Broccoli"
      ],
      "question": "Savoy And Late Flat Dutch Are Both Varieties Of Which Vegetable?",
      "tags": [
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "correctAnswer": "A Sow",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "A Gander",
        "A Jenny",
        "A Hen"
      ],
      "question": "What is a female pig known as?",
      "tags": [
        "animals",
        "biology",
        "names",
        "science"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Film & TV",
      "correctAnswer": "Monsters, Inc.",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Metropolis",
        "Into the Wild",
        "The Green Mile"
      ],
      "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'In order to power the city, beasts have to scare children so that they scream.'",
      "tags": [
        "film",
        "film_and_tv"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "correctAnswer": "Illinois ",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Michigan",
        "Indiana",
        "Ohio"
      ],
      "question": "In which US state is Chicago",
      "tags": [
        "usa",
        "chicago",
        "us_states",
        "geography"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "correctAnswer": "Cuba",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Jamaica",
        "Haiti",
        "Dominican Republic"
      ],
      "question": "In Which Country Will You Find The Bay Of Pigs?",
      "tags": [
        "places",
        "geography"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "correctAnswer": "Blue",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Black",
        "Orange",
        "White"
      ],
      "question": "Which of these colors is included on the flag of Ukraine?",
      "tags": [
        "flags",
        "geography"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Film & TV",
      "correctAnswer": "\"A census taker once tried to test me. I ate his liver with some fava beans and a nice Chianti.\"",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "\"Attica! Attica!\"",
        "\"Chewie, we’re home.\"",
        "\"What is this? A center for ants? How can we be expected to teach children to learn how to read…if they can’t even fit inside the building?\""
      ],
      "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'The Silence of the Lambs'?",
      "tags": [
        "film",
        "quotes",
        "general_knowledge",
        "film_and_tv"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "correctAnswer": "Taiwan",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "South Korea",
        "Malaysia",
        "Philippines"
      ],
      "question": "Tainan is a city in which country?",
      "tags": [
        "cities",
        "geography"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "correctAnswer": "numbers",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "wounds and injuries caused by accidents or assaults and their surgical treatment and repair",
          "psychotropic or psychiatric drugs",
          "Egyptian hieroglyphics, an ancient writing system"
        ],
        "question": "What is Numerology the study of?",
        "tags": [
          "science"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "Geography",
        "correctAnswer": "Portuguese ",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Spanish",
          "English",
          "French"
        ],
        "question": "What Is The Main Language Spoken In Brazil?",
        "tags": [
          "language",
          "south_america",
          "geography"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "History",
        "correctAnswer": "The Titanic",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "The Majestic",
          "The Enormous",
          "The Colossus"
        ],
        "question": "Which British Liner Sank On Its Maiden Voyage In 1912?",
        "tags": [
          "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "Sport & Leisure",
        "correctAnswer": "Football",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Hockey",
          "Tennis",
          "Surfing"
        ],
        "question": "With which sport is David Beckham associated?",
        "tags": [
          "people",
          "general_knowledge",
          "sport"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "History",
        "correctAnswer": "Holocaust",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Auchterarder",
          "Blitzkrieg",
          "Luftwaffe"
        ],
        "question": "Which word describes the Nazi genocide of Jews?",
        "tags": [
          "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "History",
        "correctAnswer": "George Washington ",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Chester Arthur",
          "Ulysses S. Grant",
          "Millard Fillmore"
        ],
        "question": "Who was the 1st president of the USA, in term during the period 1789–1797?",
        "tags": [
          "presidents",
          "usa",
          "firsts",
          "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Madonna",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Eric Clapton",
          "Nicki Minaj",
          "Alanis Morissette"
        ],
        "question": "Who sung 'Material Girl'?",
        "tags": [
          "songs",
          "musicians",
          "general_knowledge",
          "music"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "Sport & Leisure",
        "correctAnswer": "Basketball",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Volleyball",
          "Football",
          "Baseball"
        ],
        "question": "What Sport Do The Harlem Globetrotters Play?",
        "tags": [
          "sport"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "Geography",
        "correctAnswer": "The Richter Scale ",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "The Geiger Scale",
          "The Scoville Scale",
          "The Bristol Scale"
        ],
        "question": "What Scale Is Used To Measure The Intensity Of An Earthquake",
        "tags": [
          "geology",
          "words",
          "geography"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "Society & Culture",
        "correctAnswer": "2 Turtle Doves",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "2 Ladies Dancing",
          "2 Fresh Apples",
          "2 Mocking Birds"
        ],
        "question": "What Did My True Love Give To Me On The \"Second\" Day Of Christmas?",
        "tags": [
          "christmas",
          "lyrics",
          "society_and_culture"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "Film & TV",
        "correctAnswer": "An NYPD officer tries to save his wife taken hostage by terrorists during a Christmas party.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "In a post-apocalyptic wasteland, a woman rebels against a tyrannical ruler.",
          "The story of how the scandal of child molestation within the Boston Catholic church was uncovered.",
          "A rat makes an unusual alliance with a young kitchen worker at a famous restaurant."
        ],
        "question": "What is the plot of the movie Die Hard?",
        "tags": [
          "film",
          "film_and_tv"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "Society & Culture",
        "correctAnswer": "Medusa",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Minotaur",
          "Harpy",
          "Siren"
        ],
        "question": "Which Ancient Greek creature had snakes for hair?",
        "tags": [
          "mythology",
          "ancient_greece",
          "society_and_culture"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "Film & TV",
        "correctAnswer": "Tom Hanks",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Ewan McGregor",
          "Will Smith",
          "Tom Cruise"
        ],
        "question": "Which actor has featured in films including Forrest Gump and Apollo 13?",
        "tags": [
          "film",
          "acting",
          "film_and_tv"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "Sport & Leisure",
        "correctAnswer": "Football",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Snooker",
          "Cricket",
          "Motor racing"
        ],
        "question": "With which sport is Cristiano Ronaldo associated?",
        "tags": [
          "people",
          "general_knowledge",
          "sport"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "correctAnswer": "The Hunger Games",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Voyages Extraordinaires",
          "Harry Potter",
          "Mortal Engines Quartet"
        ],
        "question": "In which book series does 'Katniss Everdeen' appear?",
        "tags": [
          "young_adult",
          "literature",
          "fictitious_characters",
          "general_knowledge",
          "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Michael Jackson",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Nicki Minaj",
          "Neil Young",
          "Eric Clapton"
        ],
        "question": "Which American singer, songwriter and dancer released the song 'Don't Stop 'Til You Get Enough'?",
        "tags": [
          "songs",
          "music"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "Science",
        "correctAnswer": "Charles Darwin",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Albert Einstein",
          "Marie Curie",
          "Francis Crick"
        ],
        "question": "Who fist proposed the theory of evolution?",
        "tags": [
          "people",
          "biology",
          "general_knowledge",
          "science"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "Geography",
        "correctAnswer": "Brazil",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Spain",
          "Egypt",
          "Argentina"
        ],
        "question": "In which country would you find the city of Rio de Janeiro?",
        "tags": [
          "cities",
          "general_knowledge",
          "geography"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "Society & Culture",
        "correctAnswer": "Olympus",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Sinai",
          "Everest",
          "Marathon"
        ],
        "question": "Which Greek mountain was known as the home of the gods?",
        "tags": [
          "mythology",
          "ancient_greece",
          "classics",
          "general_knowledge",
          "society_and_culture"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Michael Jackson",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Nicki Minaj",
          "Neil Young",
          "Eric Clapton"
        ],
        "question": "Which American musician sung 'Rock with You'?",
        "tags": [
          "songs",
          "music"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy"
      },
      {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "correctAnswer": "Deipnophobia",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Cacophony",
          "Cabotage",
          "Futz"
        ],
        "question": "Which word is defined as 'a morbid fear of dinner parties'?",
        "tags": [
          "words",
          "general_knowledge"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "Geography",
        "correctAnswer": "Timor-Leste",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Grenada",
          "Kuwait",
          "Romania"
        ],
        "question": "Dili is the capital city of which country?",
        "tags": [
          "capital_cities",
          "geography"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "Sport & Leisure",
        "correctAnswer": "Winnipeg Jets",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Winnipeg Padres",
          "Winnipeg Broncos",
          "Winnipeg Penguins"
        ],
        "question": "Which of these is a hockey team based in Winnipeg?",
        "tags": [
          "sport"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "Geography",
        "correctAnswer": "USA",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Croatia",
          "Spain",
          "Australia"
        ],
        "question": "In which country would you find the Carlsbad Caverns National Park?",
        "tags": [
          "tourist_attractions",
          "geography"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "Film & TV",
        "correctAnswer": "Jeff Bridges",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Clark Gregg",
          "Paul Rudd",
          "Sebastian Stan"
        ],
        "question": "Who plays the role of Obadiah Stane in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?",
        "tags": [
          "mcu",
          "film",
          "acting",
          "marvel",
          "comics",
          "film_and_tv"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "correctAnswer": "Little Women",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Buddenbrooks",
          "David Copperfield",
          "Jane Eyre"
        ],
        "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line ''Christmas won't be Christmas without any presents''?",
        "tags": [
          "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "Sport & Leisure",
        "correctAnswer": "Germany",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Russia",
          "South Africa",
          "South Korea & Japan"
        ],
        "question": "Which country hosted the 2006 FIFA World Cup?",
        "tags": [
          "world_cup",
          "football",
          "soccer",
          "sport"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "Geography",
        "correctAnswer": "Yamoussoukro",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Male",
          "Bamako",
          "Moroni"
        ],
        "question": "What is the capital city of Cote d'Ivoire?",
        "tags": [
          "geography"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "correctAnswer": "Charles Dickens",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Oscar Wilde",
          "Joseph Conrad",
          "Henryk Sienkiewicz"
        ],
        "question": "Which author wrote 'Dombey and Son'?",
        "tags": [
          "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "History",
        "correctAnswer": "1971",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "1957",
          "1964",
          "1978"
        ],
        "question": "When was the first email sent?",
        "tags": [
          "events",
          "firsts",
          "technology",
          "the_internet",
          "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "Sport & Leisure",
        "correctAnswer": "Oxford",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Manchester",
          "London",
          "York"
        ],
        "question": "In which English city did Roger Bannister become the first man to run a mile in under 4 minutes? ",
        "tags": [
          "sport"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "Science",
        "correctAnswer": "A herd",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "A sloth",
          "A skulk",
          "A cete"
        ],
        "question": "What is the word for a group of giraffes?",
        "tags": [
          "science"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "Sport & Leisure",
        "correctAnswer": "Pete Sampras",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Roger Federer",
          "Lleyton Hewitt",
          "Andy Roddick"
        ],
        "question": "Who Won The US Open Men's Tennis Title in 1990 At The Age Of Just 19?",
        "tags": [
          "tennis",
          "people",
          "1990's",
          "sport"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "correctAnswer": "A Study in Scarlet",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "The Murder of Roger Ackroyd",
          "The Shadow of the Wind",
          "Inferno"
        ],
        "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'In the year 1878 I took my degree of Doctor of Medicine of the University of London, and proceeded to Netley to go through the course prescribed for surgeons in the army.'?",
        "tags": [
          "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "Food & Drink",
        "correctAnswer": "Fettuccine",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Orecchiette",
          "Lasagne",
          "Cavatappi"
        ],
        "question": "Which pasta's name means 'Little ribbons'?",
        "tags": [
          "food",
          "words",
          "language",
          "food_and_drink"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Iron Maiden",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Deep Purple",
          "Feeder",
          "Squeeze"
        ],
        "question": "Which band includes 'Steve Harris'?",
        "tags": [
          "music"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "Science",
        "correctAnswer": "Guglielmo Marconi",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Samuel Morse",
          "Alexander Graham Bell",
          "Michael Faraday"
        ],
        "question": "Who first transmitted radio signals across the Atlantic?",
        "tags": [
          "science"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "Geography",
        "correctAnswer": "Asia",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Europe",
          "Africa",
          "Autralasia"
        ],
        "question": "In which continent would you find the Ob river?",
        "tags": [
          "rivers",
          "bodies_of_water",
          "geography"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "Geography",
        "correctAnswer": "Hiratsuka",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Ōsaka",
          "Kyoto",
          "Yokohama"
        ],
        "question": "Which city used to be called Suba?",
        "tags": [
          "cities",
          "geography"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      },
      {
        "category": "History",
        "correctAnswer": "160",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "0",
          "50",
          "300"
        ],
        "question": "Approximately how many children did pharaoh Ramses II father?",
        "tags": [
          "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard"
      }
  ]